Alright, we'll the SNS uh, topic now, uh,
what an s is, what a topic is.
All that is covered in the deep dive course.
You can take a look at that course over there.
So we'll first go to SNS and click on SNS.
You will then go to topics on the left hand side
and then click here, create topic,
and then choose standard, then topic, mission, D-E-H-H-O-F,
and then scroll down and simply create the topic.
Next, scroll down.
If you subscription here, click on the orange button,
create subscription, and then choose the protocol as email.
You wanna get an email, right email
and then provide your email address.
So I'll provide mine and then click on the orange button,
create subscription, and then scroll down.
You don't see anything here. Go to subscriptions.
On the left hand side, you scroll down,
yours will show pending confirmation.
So go to your email. So you gotta order an email like this.
In that email you'll have a link to confirm subscription.
So click on that and it'll say subscription confirmed when
you go back to your subscriptions.
And do a refresh of the page right here and scroll down.
You should see your email subscription being confirmed.
That's it. Get this done
and uh, we'll see you in the next video.